so when they diagnosed me i was at a three and now i'm at a two i keep sketching it down and
and pretty soon it's going to be no evidence of disease i have a clearer path now because
of everything i've learned so i know better what to do and i've never felt like your face feels
it's never been this has been really eye-opening and for someone who likes to be their own guinea
pig really really why are you crying oh my god i'm proud of you you're crying for pride okay
you're gonna make me cry when people because that's like don't cry for fear fear no i'm so
proud of you because you like performed alchemy on yourself you know and i don't think a lot of
people understand or really really truly understand like the magic that you can create within your body
like that's magic you know like it's not like some far-fetched thing like you really did that like
i did that girl like ananda i remember when this news had come out for for us it's news for you
it's reality